{
    "id": "a5fecee753924d36bf3deac56b1cb489",
    "title": "Tense Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They had been waiting for the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "past perfect tense active",
                "past perfect continuous active",
                "past perfect passive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8051556056f2448a8c7f13defe367b77"
        },
        {
            "question": "India has not won many Olympic gold medals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "present perfect passive",
                "present perfect active",
                "past perfect active"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16a166f25c3645a592cb751cd0197878"
        },
        {
            "question": "The film was not interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "past continuous active",
                "past continuous passive",
                "simple past active"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b046049076545059a296e1a7556b4b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy was punished for lying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple past active",
                "simple past passive",
                "past perfect active"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "175490c2e9ed4976b0ce41f1f0e8f7dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your order has been shipped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "present perfect active",
                "present perfect passive",
                "simple present active",
                "simple past active"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ca8ef54514e4ba9b56397eb662bd26e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house is being built by masons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "present continuous active",
                "present continuous passive",
                "past continuous active"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d39730b5b4204368b2f5f91f00eb5a19"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who are you waiting for?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "present continuous tense active",
                "present continuous tense passive",
                "simple past active"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab116d1891e947e7bc33982ff0b7e289"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been living in this street for well over ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "present continuous tense active",
                "present perfect tense passive",
                "present perfect continuous tense active"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "59cdeb4ab2a94aefb1018cb752d4ba81"
        },
        {
            "question": "Trains will be running late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple future tense active",
                "simple future tense passive",
                "future continuous tense active",
                "future continuous tense passive"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "560e6645f4ce4d1da88ea57b5576139b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news is too good to be true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple present active",
                "simple present passive",
                "simple past active"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f941eed7f4354374a4cfc990d81f0f33"
        }
    ]
}